

#### **PROFILE**

Four years of professional experience. Energetic and adept at problem-solving, with a proactive and collaborative mindset, complemented by strong technical and analytical skills, as well as excellent communication abilities. Quick learner with a keen aptitude for anticipating challenges.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Master Computer Network and IOT System

2022-2024(Expected)
Conservatoire national des arts et métier (CNAM), Paris, France

Courses: Al for Networks & IoT, Network Virtualization and Automation, Embedded Systems: Applications, Internet of things Project: NWDAF (Demonstration of a Network Data Analytics function)

# **Bachelor of Computer Science**

2014-2018

University of Science and Technology, Mazandaran, Iran

#### **CONTACT**

#### WEBSITE:

https://fatemeh-

salmani1.github.io/FatemehTheAnalyst.github.io/

#### LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fatemeh-salmani

#### **EMAIL**:

Salmanifatemeh1996@gmail.com

#### **ADDRESS:**

244 Rue de Bercy, 75012 Paris, France

PHONE:

+33667836642

#### **REFERENCES**

stefano.secci@cnam.fr University professor pedro.velloso@cnam.fr University professor

# **FATEMEH SALMANI**

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# DATA ANALYSIS INTERN LABORATOIRE D'INFORMATIQUE DU CNAM(CEDRIC), FRANCE

Jun 2023-Sep2023

(Libraries used: Pandas, Matplotlib, Tadm, Math)

- Data Preprocessing and Cleaning using SQL, Excel and GCP (Google Cloud Platform)
- Geospatial Data Analysis with Python
- Proximity Analysis and Data Visualization
- Quantitative Data Insights
- Optimization through Data-Driven Decision Making

## WEB DEVELOPER ROUZBAHAN COLLEGE, IRAN

2020-2022

- Coded and provided ongoing support for websites postimplementation
- Well-versed in matters related to E-learning, contributing to the development and management of E-learning solutions

# WEB DESIGNER AND PROGRAMMER ADVERTISING AGENCIES OF IRANIANUK118, IRAN

2018-2020

- Produced efficient and elegant code with Python, SQL, JavaScript, CSS and HTML
- Created motion graphics, short animations, and various graphic design assets using Adobe After Effects, Photoshop, and Illustrator

#### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

- Languages and Frameworks: Python, R, SQL, Julia
- Data Visualization: Tableau, R (ggplot2, Plotly)
- Data Analysis Tools: GCP, Microsoft Excel, Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate
- Web: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Operating system: Assembly Language, Linux, Apple macOS, Windows
- Network protocols: TCP/IP, UDP, DNS, http, SMTP
   Others: Adobe After Effect, Photoshop, Illustrator

## **LANGUAGE**

**English:** Full professional proficiency

French: Level B1+
Persian: Native